Bangkok, Thailand tinmaungzin.tmz@gmail.com +66931588496

Tin Maung Zin

linkedin.com/in/tinmaungzin github.com/tinmaungzin Personal Website

I am a software engineer with around 6 years of experience who is passionate about technology. Throughout my career, I have built and managed systems from small to large in the automotive, financial, and supermarket industries. I have worked with project managers and product teams, implementing solutions in the cloud, and working with several technologies and services.

Work Experience

Software Engineer	N-Spiral,	Mar 2022 – June 2024
	Myanmar	

Technologies and Languages: React, Golang, Python, Next.js, Laravel, Node.js, RabbitMQ, Redis, Terraform, Docker and Git

• Developed and maintained multiple full-stack apps using Laravel, Golang, Node.js and Next.js, including restaurant booking, gym POS, e-commerce, and insurance management.

Full-Stack Developer Nexstack, Aug 2021 – Feb 2022
Singapore

Technologies and Languages: Typescript, React.js, Next.js, MySQL, Strapi, AWS, Docker and Git

- Led a team of five developers to develop and maintain ERP solutions for supermarkets and security companies.
- Co-designed and developed a modern serverless insurance agent solution with AWS and Next.is.
- Deployed web applications using CI/CD technology with Github actions.

Web Developer Mounts Digital, May 2019 – June 2021

Myanmar

Technologies and Languages: PHP (Laravel), Javascript (Vue.js, JQuery), Vuex, MySQL and Git

- Implemented back-and-forth data flows between multiple components using Vue.js and Vuex technologies.
- I co-designed and developed an interactive and complex POS system for a money exchange business.
- Developed two advanced ERPs with accounting, finance, multi-role authorization, and comprehensive reporting.

Internship Studio AMK, Nov 2018 – Feb 2019
Myanmar

Technologies and Languages: Node.js, Express.js, HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL and Git

- Designed and developed a company internal solution with HTML and CSS.
- Built and tested football live score and movie database applications using Node.js and Express.js.
- I created a promotion campaign module as a part of an existing microservice application.

Technologies and Languages

• Languages: PHP (Laravel), Javascript (Vue.js, React.js, Next.js, Node.js), Python, Golang

• Technologies: MySQL, Postgres, Docker, AWS, and Git

Education